An ordinary boy, an extraordinary faith.
Light of the World is a animation, fantasy, drama film directed by Tom Bancroft.
It's 30 AD and everyone is expectantly awaiting the coming Messiah.
While Jesus isn't exactly what they imagined, there
is something special about this man.
Soon, John, James, Andrew, Peter, and others begin to
follow Jesus on an unexpected adventure.
This beautifully animated story of Jesus is told through the eyes
of his beloved young friend, the Apostle John.
Jesus (voice), played by Ian Hanlin.
John (voice), played by Benjamin Jacobson.
Andrew (voice), played by Vincent Tong.
Nicodemus (voice), played by Michael Benyaer.
Judas Iscariot (voice), played by David Kaye.
Pharisee (voice), played by Peter New.
The Light (German: Das Licht) is a 2025 drama film written and directed by
Tom Tykwer and starring Lars Eidinger and Nicolette Krebitz.
The film depicts the everyday life of a middle-class
family in a world that has become unstable.
The German-French co-production also have Elke Biesendorfer,
Julius Gause and Elyas Eldridge in pivotal roles.
The film premiered at the 75th Berlin International Film
Festival in Special Gala section on 13 February 2025.
It was released on 20 March 2025 in German theatres by X Verleih.
The film explores themes of bible, religious film, jesus
christ, christian film, christian faith.
The tone is emotional.